<resources>

    <!-- Donation -->
    <string name="donation_home_tile_title">Donate</string>
    <string name="donation_home_tile_subtitle">Support a cause</string>
    <string name="donate_intro_title">Support your favorite charities</string>
    <string name="donate_intro_body">Donate to support local and global charities right from your phone. Just tap, give, and smile.</string>
    <string name="donate_intro_next">Let\'s Go</string>
    <string name="donate_location_turn_on_location_services">Turn on Location Services</string>
    <string name="donate_location_body">Change your device settings so you can see nearby places that accept fast, secure payments with PayPal.</string>
    <string name="donate_skip">Skip</string>
    <string name="donate_next">Next</string>
    <string name="donate_search_hint">Find a charity</string>
    <string name="donate_tab_for_you">For You</string>
    <string name="donate_tab_popular">Popular</string>
    <string name="donate_see_nearby_charities_subject">See nearby charities</string>
    <string name="donate_see_nearby_charities_text">It\'s easy to support local charities. Just enable location services to see how you can make a difference nearby.</string>
    <string name="donate_popular_footer_text">Search for other charities you can support through PayPal Giving Fund</string>
    <string name="donate_type_featured">Featured</string>
    <string name="donate_type_all">All Charities</string>
    <string name="donate_type_nearby">Nearby</string>
    <string name="donate_type_search_results">Search Results</string>
    <string name="donate_charity_ein">EIN: %1$s&#8210;%2$s</string>
    <string name="donate_charity_number">Charity Number: %1$s</string>
    <string name="donate_au_abn">ABN: %1$s</string>
    <string name="donate_ca_cra">CRA number: %1$s</string>
    <string name="donate_us_ppgf_disclaimer">PayPal covers all transaction costs for donations made on this site, ensuring that 100%% of each gift made is available to charity. Your donation will be made to PayPal Giving Fund, an IRS&#8208;registered 501(c)(3) public charity (Federal Tax ID: 45&#8208;0931286). PayPal Giving Fund will provide the receipt for your donation, which is subject to its &lt;a href=&quot;%1$s&quot;&gt;donor terms of service&lt;/a&gt;. We verify that receiving charities have tax-exempt status with the IRS and are not on recognized economic sanctions lists. Charities enrolled with PayPal Giving Fund will typically receive funds in their PayPal accounts within 15 to 45 days after PayPal Giving Fund’s receipt of a donation. Charities not enrolled with PayPal Giving Fund will be additionally vetted and if eligible, will receive funds via other means, such as a check, typically within 90 days. PayPal Giving Fund holds all donations in a non-interest bearing account. PayPal Giving Fund retains ultimate discretion over all donations it receives and, in limited cases, may redirect funds when a charity does not meet legal or other eligibility requirements as described in its &lt;a href=&quot;%2$s&quot;&gt;Nonprofit Certification Policy&lt;/a&gt;.</string>
    <string name="donate_gb_ppgf_enrolled_disclaimer"><![CDATA[PayPal helps your gifts do more good. Your donation will be made to PayPal Giving Fund UK, a registered charity (No. 1110538). PayPal Giving Fund will email you a donation receipt with a link to add Gift Aid. Thanks to PayPal’s support, PayPal Giving Fund passes on 100%% of donations it collects on this site to worthy causes.<br /><br />The charity you recommend will typically receive the funds within 15-45 days of your original donation. This doesn’t happen often, but we may not be able to deliver the funds to the charity you recommend. If so, we’ll ask you to recommend another charity before reassigning the funds. ]]>For more information, please see PayPal Giving Fund’s &lt;a href=&quot;%1$s&quot;&gt;Donation Delivery Policy&lt;/a&gt;.</string>
    <string name="donate_gb_ppgf_unenrolled_disclaimer"><![CDATA[PayPal helps your gifts do more good. Your donation will be made to PayPal Giving Fund UK, a registered charity (No. 1110538). PayPal Giving Fund will email you a donation receipt with a link to add Gift Aid. Thanks to PayPal’s support, PayPal Giving Fund passes on 100%% of donations it collects on this site to worthy causes. <br /><br /> The charity you recommend will typically receive the funds within 90 days of your original donation, or within 15-45 days if it enrols with PayPal Giving Fund. This doesn’t happen often, but we may not be able to deliver the funds to the charity you recommend. If so, we’ll ask you to recommend another charity before reassigning the funds. ]]>For more information, please see PayPal Giving Fund’s &lt;a href=&quot;%1$s&quot;&gt;Donation Delivery Policy&lt;/a&gt;.</string>
    <string name="donate_au_ppgf_disclaimer">Your donation will be made to PayPal Giving Fund (ABN 65 105 950 945), a Public Ancillary Fund and a charity registered with the Australian Charities and Not-for-profits Commission (ACNC). For more information, see &lt;a href=&quot;%1$s&quot;&gt;our policies&lt;/a&gt;.</string>
    <string name="donate_ca_ppgf_disclaimer">PayPal covers all transaction costs for donations made on this site, ensuring that 100%% of each gift made is available to charity. Your donation will be made to PayPal Giving Fund Canada, a charity registered with the Canada Revenue Agency (CRA# 081286775RR0001). PayPal Giving Fund Canada will provide the receipt for your donation, which is subject to its &lt;a href=&quot;%1$s&quot;&gt;donor terms of service&lt;/a&gt;. We verify that receiving charities have registered charity status with the Canada Revenue Agency and are not on recognized economic sanctions lists. Charities enrolled with PayPal Giving Fund Canada will typically receive funds in their PayPal accounts within 15 to 45 days after PayPal Giving Fund Canada’s receipt of a donation. Charities not enrolled with PayPal Giving Fund Canada will be additionally vetted and if eligible, will receive funds via other means, such as a cheque, typically within 90 days. PayPal Giving Fund Canada holds all donations in a non-interest bearing account. PayPal Giving Fund Canada retains ultimate discretion over all donations it receives and, in limited cases, may redirect funds when a charity does not meet legal or other eligibility requirements as described in its &lt;a href=&quot;%2$s&quot;&gt;Charity Certification Policy&lt;/a&gt;.</string>
    <string name="donate_disclaimer_default">Your donation will be made to %1$s the entity described in this page. By clicking the Donate button below and selecting the value of your donation, you accept to proceed with the described donation to the aforementioned Charity.</string>
    <string name="donate_policy_webview_header">PayPal Giving Fund Policy</string>
    <string name="donate_charity_city_state">%1$s, %2$s</string>
    <string name="donate_charity_website">Visit website</string>
    <string name="donate_charity_bookmark">Bookmark charity</string>
    <string name="donate_charity_source">Source: %1$s</string>
    <string name="paypal_giving_fund">PayPal Giving Fund profile</string>
    <string name="charity_commission_public_information">Charity Commission public information</string>
    <string name="australian_charities_and_not_for_profits_commission">Australian Charities and Not-for-profits Commission (ACNC)</string>
    <string name="canada_revenue_agency">Canada Revenue Agency (CRA)</string>
    <string name="donate_minimum">Minimum donation %1$s</string>
    <string name="donate_share_user_info_us">Share my name and email with this charity.</string>
    <string name="donate_share_user_info_uk_enrolled">Share your name and email with this charity so they can acknowledge your donation.</string>
    <string name="donate_share_user_info_uk_un_enrolled">Share your name and email with this charity if they enrol in PayPal Giving Fund.</string>
    <string name="donate_share_user_info_au">Share my name and email address with the charity. If you tick this box, your recommended charity may contact you.</string>
    <string name="donate_share_user_info_ca_enrolled">Share my name, email address and donation details with my recommended charity so they may contact me.</string>
    <string name="donate_share_user_info_ca_un_enrolled">Share my name, email address and donation details with my recommended charity so they may contact me, if they enroll in PayPal Giving Fund.</string>
    <string name="donate_description">Donation via PayPal Giving Fund for %1$s</string>
    <string name="donate_description_global">Donation for %1$s</string>
    <string name="donate_webview_header_default">Donate with PayPal Giving Fund</string>
    <string name="donate_webview_header_global">Donate with PayPal</string>
    <string name="donate_done">Done</string>
    <string name="donate_more">Donate Again</string>
    <string name="donate_ok">OK</string>
    <string name="donate_success_title">You donated %1$s</string>
    <string name="donate_success_title_2">You donated %1$s to %2$s</string>
    <string name="donate_success_title_3">Thanks for your donation</string>
    <string name="donate_success_details">Your generosity will help further a cause you care about.</string>
    <string name="donate_success_share_this_cause">Share This Cause</string>
    <string name="donate_success_share_title">Donate with PayPal Giving Fund</string>
    <string name="donate_success_share_text">I donated to support %1$s. You can, too. Together we can make a difference. %2$s</string>
    <string name="donate_success_view_activity">See your donation in Activity</string>
    <string name="donate_pending_title">Your donation is pending</string>
    <string name="donate_pending_details">Regulations require us to review this payment. We\'ll update you on the status of your donation within 24&#8211;72 hours.</string>
    <string name="donate_pending_view_activity">View transaction in your Activity</string>
    <string name="donate_empty_header">Check back soon</string>
    <string name="donate_empty_text">We\'re adding new charities all the time.</string>
    <string name="donate_error_message">Looks like something went wrong on our end. Please try again. </string>
    <string name="donate_alert_dialog_title">Are you sure?</string>
    <string name="donate_alert_dialog_text"> Do you want to go back? </string>
    <string name="donate_alert_dialog_invalid_link_title">Good cause, bad link</string>
    <string name="donate_alert_dialog_invalid_link_text">It looks like someone shared a charity with you, but copied the web address wrong. Try searching for the charity.</string>
    <string name="donate_try_again">Let\’s try that again</string>
    <string name="accessibility_donate_webview_leave">Leave donation site</string>
    <string name="accessibility_donate_clear">Clear</string>
    <string name="url_us_donation_paypal_giving_fund_nonprofit_certification_policy" translatable="false">https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/givingfund/policies/nonprofit-certification-policy</string>
    <string name="url_us_donor_terms_of_service" translatable="false">https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/givingfund/policies/donor-terms-of-service</string>
    <string name="url_gb_donation_donation_delivery_policy" translatable="false">https://www.paypal.com/uk/webapps/mpp/givingfund/policies</string>
    <string name="url_au_policy" translatable="false">https://www.paypal.com/au/webapps/mpp/givingfund/policies/privacy-policy?locale.x=en_AU</string>
    <string name="url_ca_donor_terms_of_service" translatable="false">https://www.paypal.com/ca/webapps/mpp/givingfund/policies/donor-terms-of-service</string>
    <string name="url_ca_donor_charity_certification_policy" translatable="false">https://www.paypal.com/ca/webapps/mpp/givingfund/policies/charity-certification-policy</string>
    <string name="url_donation_share" translatable="false">https://www.paypal.com/fundraiser/charity/%1$s</string>
    <string name="donate_charity_list_error_header">Unable to load</string>
    <string name="donate_charity_list_error">Looks like something went wrong on our end. Please try again in a moment.</string>
</resources>
